BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail
  - Retail Clerks International Union, 1935-1938 (Box 130, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: D. H. Schulte, Inc. and Retail Cigar Salesmen's Union, Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Locals 906, 961, 963, 934, 874, AFL, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 31)
      Agreement effective 9/14/1936 and expires on 11/30/1937. Covers 834 workers in New York, NY; New Haven, CT; Jersey City; NJ; Philadelphia, PA; Boston, MA
    - Item 2: Safeway Stores, Bilow Stores, Miller Stores, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 7, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 31)
      Agreement effective 8/2/1937 and expires on 8/1/1938. Covers 850 workers in Denver, CO
    - Item 3: Food Employers Association and Retail Food Clerks Union, Local 870, Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Locals 1179 and 1058, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 31)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1937 and expires on 9/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Oakland, CA
    - Item 4: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 512, AFL, 1937-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 31)
      Agreement effective 9/27/1937 and expires on 1/1/1939. Covers 50 workers in Watsonville, CA
    - Item 5: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 883, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 31)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1938 and expires on 1/1/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in unknown
  - Retail Clerks International Union, 1937-1939 (Box 130, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Vallejo Retail Grocery and Food Merchants and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 373, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 32)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 1/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Vallejo, CA
    - Item 2: Retail Grocers' Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 428, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 32)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1937 and expires on 2/28/1938. Covers 300 workers in San Jose, CA
    - Item 3: Automobile Salesmen's Union, Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 428, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 32)
      Agreement effective 8/16/1937 and expires on 8/16/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in San Jose, CA
    - Item 4: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 113, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 32)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1938 and expires on 2/28/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Santa Rosa, CA
  - Retail Clerks International Union, Local 47, 1938 (Box 130, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 47, AFL, Central Labor Council of Alameda County, Addendum, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 1/3/1938 and expires on 1/1/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Oakland, CA
  - Retail Clerks Union, 1937-1938 (Box 130, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: St. Louis House Furniture Company, Schauk Furniture Company, Spiker Furniture Company, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 403, AFL, 1935-1927; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 34)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1935 and expires on 1/1/1927. Covers 105 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 2: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 2, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 34)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 1/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Paul, MN
    - Item 3: Beaty Stores, Kennedy's Grocery Company, Schenecker's Market, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 988, AFL, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 34)
      Agreement effective 3/23/1938 and expires on 3/23/1939. Covers 136 workers in St. Joseph, MO
    - Item 4: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 655, AFL, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 34)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1938 and expires on 4/27/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Louis, MO
  - Retail Clerks Union, 1936-1938 (Box 130, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: Silver Bow Employers' Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 4, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 35)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1936 and expires on 5/1/1937. Covers 68 workers in Butte, MT
    - Item 2: Star Square Auto Supply Company and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 403, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 35)
      Agreement effective 5/15/1937 and expires on 5/14/1938. Covers 36 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 3: Silver Bow Employers' Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 4, 1937-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 35)
      Agreement effective 6/7/1937 and expires on 5/1/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Butte, MT
    - Item 4: Anaconda Employers' Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1041, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 35)
      Agreement effective 6/16/1937 and expires on 6/15/1938. Covers 130-150 workers in Anaconda, MT
  - Retail Clerks Union, 1937-1938 (Box 130, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: Deer Lodge Employer's Association, Inc. and Deer Lodge Clerks' Union, Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1235, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 36)
      Agreement effective 6/15/1937 and expires on 6/15/1938. Covers 50 workers in Deer Lodge, MT
    - Item 2: Eagle Grocery Company and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1245, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 36)
      Agreement effective 8/30/1937 and expires on 8/29/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Jersey City, NJ
    - Item 3: Havre Industrial Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 171, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 36)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1938 and expires on 2/28/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Havre, MT
    - Item 4: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1427, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 36)
      Agreement effective 6/15/1938 and expires on 12/15/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Kalispell, MT
  - Retail Clerks Union, 1937-1938 (Box 130, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 880, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 37)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 1/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cincinnati, OH
    - Item 2: Members of the Retail Merchants' Division, East Liverpool Chamber of Commerce and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 133, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 37)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1937 and expires on 4/1/1938. Covers 150 workers in East Liverpool, OH
    - Item 3: Eagle Grocery Company and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1245, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 37)
    - Item 4: Euclid Coffee Company and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1163, AFL, Addendum, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 37)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 11/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cleveland, OH
  - Retail Clerks International Association, 1937-1939 (Box 130, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: Nelsonville Merchants Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 887, 1937-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 38)
      Agreement effective 4/13/1937 and expires on 4/13/1939. Covers 107 workers in Nelsonville, OH
    - Item 2: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 863, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 38)
      Agreement effective 4/19/1937 and expires on 4/18/1938. Covers 50 workers in Barberton, OH
    - Item 3: Crawford Clothes, Inc. and Retail Clothing Salesmen's Union, Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1006, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 38)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1937 and expires on 8/31/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 4: Bellaire Merchants' Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 126, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 38)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1938 and expires on 4/1/1939. Covers 108 workers in Bellaire, OH
  - Retail Clerks Union, 1937 (Box 130, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Lion Store and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 128, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 39)
      Agreement effective 12/1/1936 and expires on 10/1/1937. Covers 330 workers in Toledo, OH
    - Item 2: Home Furniture Company and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 128, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 39)
      Agreement effective 2/4/1937 and expires on 2/1/1938. Covers 7 workers in Toledo, OH
    - Item 3: S. S. Kresge Company and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 128, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 39)
      Agreement effective 3/15/1937 and expires on 3/15/1938. Covers 60 workers in Toledo, OH
    - Item 4: Galperin Brothers, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 128, 1937-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 39)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1937 and expires on 10/1/1937. Covers 8 workers in Toledo, OH
    - Item 5: Krohngold's, Walter's, Wachter's, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 128, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 39)
      Agreement effective 4/13/1937 and expires on 4/12/1938. Covers 65 workers in Toledo, OH
  - Retail Clerks International Association, 1937-1938 (Box 130, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: A. E. Adams Grocery, H. W. H Adams, H. J. Anderson Service Station, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 734, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 40)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1936 and expires on 9/1/1937. Covers 69 workers in St. Helen, OR
    - Item 2: Retail Merchants Association, Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1219, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 40)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1937 and expires on 10/31/1938. Covers 70 workers in El Reno, OK
    - Item 3: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1171, AFL, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 40)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1938 and expires on 6/30/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Oregon City, OR
    - Item 4: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1092, AFL, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 40)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1938 and expires on 5/1/1939. Covers 1200 workers in Portland, OR
  - Retail Clerks International Association, 1937-1938 (Box 130, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Neisner Brothers, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 257, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 41)
      Agreement effective 5/10/1937 and expires on 5/31/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in New Castle, PA
    - Item 2: N. Kaufman Food Store, Fayette Market Food Store, Acme, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 41)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1937 and expires on 9/1/1938. Covers 92 workers in Uniontown, PA
    - Item 3: American Stores Company and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1357, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 41)
      Agreement effective 9/27/1937 and expires on 9/24/1938. Covers 4000 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 4: Retail Clothing Merchants Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 42, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 41)
      Agreement effective 9/21/1937 and expires on 9/15/1938. Covers 155 workers in Philadelphia, PA
  - Retail Clerks International Association, 1936-1939 (Box 130, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: Haughton and Robins Clothing Company and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 241, 1925-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 42)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1925 and expires on 4/1/1939. Covers 158 workers in Barre, VT
    - Item 2: St. Charles Business Men's Progressive Club and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 986, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 42)
      Agreement effective 5/14/1937 and expires on 5/14/1938. Covers 21 workers in St. Charles, VA
    - Item 3: Greenfield Market, Hirsh Shoe Store, Levy's Clothing Store, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 883, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 42)
      Agreement effective 12/1/1937 and expires on 12/1/1938. Covers 87 workers in Uniontown, PA
    - Item 4: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1083, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 42)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1938 and expires on 5/1/1939. Covers 100 workers in Port Arthur, PA
  - Retail Clerks International, 1936-1938 (Box 130, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: Sprouse Rutze, A. O. Hammer and Company, Baughman's Grocery, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 847, 1936-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 43)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1936 and expires on 7/1/1938. Covers 65 workers in Camas, WA
    - Item 2: J. C. Penney Co., Montgomery Ward and Company, Smart Shop, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 375, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 43)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936 and expires on 1/1/1937. Covers an unknown number of workers in Port Angeles, WA
    - Item 3: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 240, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 43)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 11/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Bellingham, WA
    - Item 4: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 166, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 43)
      Agreement effective 12/1/1937 and expires on 12/1/1938. Covers 97 workers in South Bend, WA
  - Retail Clerks International, 1937-1939 (Box 130, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: Industrial Conference Board and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1060, AFL, Tacoma Central Labor Council, 1936-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 44)
      Agreement effective 5/16/1936 and expires on 6/1/1939. Covers 95 workers in Tacoma, WA
    - Item 2: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 367, 1937-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 44)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 11/1/1937. Covers an unknown number of workers in Tacoma, WA
    - Item 3: Tacoma Automobile Dealer's Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1048, AFL, 1937-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 44)
      Agreement effective 12/27/1937 and expires on 6/15/1939. Covers 145 workers in Tacoma, WA
    - Item 4: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 367, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 44)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 6/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Tacoma, WA
    - Item 5: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 367, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 44)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1938 and expires on 1/1/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Tacoma, WA
  - Retail Clerks International, local 1357, 1937 (Box 130, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: The American Stores Company and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1357, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 9/27/1938 and expires on 9/27/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Philadelphia, PA
  - Retail Clerks International, 1937-1938 (Box 130, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 901, 1929-1936; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 46)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1929 and expires on 1/1/1936. Covers 200 workers in East St. Louis, IL
    - Item 2: Johnson and Parks, P. J. Nee, Harry Kaupman Inc., and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 262, AFL, 1935-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 46)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1935 and expires on 1/1/1937. Covers 423 workers in Washington, DC
    - Item 3: Thom McAnn's and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 262, AFL, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 46)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936 and expires on 3/16/1937. Covers an unknown number of workers in Washington, DC
    - Item 4: Karls Shoe Stores Company and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 769, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 46)
      Agreement effective 2/15/1937 and expires on 1/1/1938. Covers 8 workers in San Diego, CA
    - Item 5: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, AFL, Birmingham Trades Council, State Federation of Labor, Local 757, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 46)
      Agreement effective 5/15/1937 and expires on 5/15/1938. Covers 55 workers in Birminghman, AL
  - Retail Clerks International, 1937 (Box 130, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: Retail Employers Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 57, 1935-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 47)
      Agreement effective 12/15/1935 and expires on 12/15/1937. Covers 387 workers in Great Falls, MT
    - Item 2: Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 380, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 47)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 1/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cleveland, OH
    - Item 3: Two Harbors Merchants' Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 930, 1937-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 47)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 12/31/1937. Covers 49 workers in Two Harbors, MN
    - Item 4: Hollywood Cotton Shop, Hooey and Morris D. J. Company, J. L. Ing. Food Store, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1263, 1937-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 47)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 12/31/1937. Covers 60 workers in Du Quoin, IL
  - Retail Clerks International, 1936-1938 (Box 130, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: Hiram Paul Clothing Company, Streeter Ready to Wear, Levines Department Store, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 518, AFL, 1935-1936; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 48)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1935 and expires on 11/18/1936. Covers 66 workers in Oklahoma City, OK
    - Item 2: Darnolds Grocery Market, Inez Arnold Grocery, West Side Grocery, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 518, AFL, 1935-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 48)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1935 and expires on 1/1/1938. Covers 59 workers in Oklahoma City, OK
    - Item 3: Dellinger Drug Company, Pharmacists and Apprentices Union and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1023, AFL, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 48)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936 and expires on 1/1/1937. Covers 250 workers in Oklahoma City, OK
    - Item 4: Merchants Association of New Straitsville, Ohio and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 989, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 48)
      Agreement effective 2/1/1937 and expires on 2/1/1938. Covers 13 workers in New Straitsville, OH
    - Item 5: High School Pharmacy, Matwood Pharmacy, Bramwood Drug Company, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1023, AFL, 1937-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 48)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1937 and expires on 12/15/1937. Covers 273 workers in Oklahoma City, OK
  - Retail Clerks International, 1938 (Box 130, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: Retail Shoe and Textile Salesmen's Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 410, 1936-1936; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 49)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936 and expires on 12/31/1936. Covers 65 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 2: Kroger Grocery and Baking Company, Woodway Stores Inc., Zeigler Store Company, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 680, 1937-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 49)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1937 and expires on 3/1/1937. Covers 32 workers in Zeigler, IL
    - Item 3: Galperin Brothers, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1050, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 49)
      Agreement effective 3/18/1937 and expires on 1/1/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Detroit, MI
    - Item 4: Coffman Fisher, Cumberland Cloak and Suit, Public Service, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 654, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 49)
      Agreement effective 5/17/1937 and expires on 3/1/1938. Covers 700 workers in Cumberland, MD
  - Retail Clerks International, 1937-1938 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Silver Bow Employers' Association and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 4, 1936-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 5/15/1936 and expires on 5/1/1939. Covers 788 workers in Butte, MT
    - Item 2: Lerner Shops of Michigan, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 1050, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 3/12/1937 and expires on 3/12/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Detroit, MI
    - Item 3: Joe's Market, George H. Harlin Market, Gill Brothers Grocery Company, and others and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 655, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 1)